# JAMILA YAQOOB DHEDHI

Cell: 03342945322

Email: nurjamila1@gmail.com

LinkedIn: LinkedIn

GitHub: GitHub

Portfolio: view my portfolio

**About** 

To be part of an organization that provides an opportunity to learn new technologies and share my knowledge with others. I would like to put my skills and expertise to the benefit of the organization. Motivated individual with strong work ethic and working independently. Strong organizational and team collaboration skills with experience in improving processes.

**Experience** 

**CodAlpha /** 10 JULY 2024 - 10 OCT 2024

Web Development

Marketing and Sales, Alboon Company / Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

- Selling Products on eBay and Amazon.
- Promoting products on Facebook Marketplace.

Data Entry Specialist, Global One Marketing/ Dec 2020 - Jan 2021

- Data Entry Work.
- Data Validation.
- Data Scraping.

Education

DHA Suffa University(Karachi, Pakistan)

Bachelor of Cybersecurity

St.John's International School(Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

A-Levels

Marefat International School(Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

**IGCSE** 

Sk Pandan Perdana (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

**UPSR** 

Language

- English
- Malay
- Urdu

## Skills

- JavaScript
- Typescript
- HTML
- CSS
- Marketing
- Social Media
- Presentation Skills
- Communication Skills
- Creative Thinker
- MS Excel
- Marketing and sales
- Nextis
- Reactjs

#### **Todo-List**

## **Currency Converter**

My currency converter project is a beginner-friendly web application designed for easy currency conversion using real-time exchange rates sourced from an external API.It's a practical tool styled for both desktop and mobile devices, aimed at providing a seamless user experience across different platforms.

#### **Age Calculator**

The Age Calculator Project is a straightforward web application designed to help users determine their age in years, months, and days based on their date of birth.

#### **Countdown Timer**

React Set Timer: A Sleek and Functional Countdown Timer. This timer features an intuitive design where you can swipe to adjust the hours, minutes, and seconds, and easily start or stop the countdown with a single click.

- Playing Badminton
- Cooking
- Reading
- English Runner Up
- Road Run Marathon

# **Projects**

Hobbies

Certificates